Fittingly, playing for pride, for the
man next to them, and for the love of
the game, all of that was enough.
Detroit sweeps the Bears this season
with a final win here at Soldier Field,
19 to 16, thanks to a walk-off field
goal winner from Jake Bates. Thanks so
much for tuning in to the Detroit Lions
Live Postgame Show presented by Keer
Auto Insurance. For the last time this
season, I'm joined by the Super Bowl
champion at Lomas Brown. I'm Dani
Rodgers. For the first time in weeks,
Detroit's ground attack looked like
itself, and the defense gave this team a
chance to win, something we saw earlier
this season when Detroit was humming,
Lomas.
>> Oh, Dani, you could see from the first
play out, this defense came ready to
play. The offense was in rhythm. Those
guys, they played hard. I'm so proud of
those guys in that locker room because,
again, really nothing to play for but
pride, like you said, and they came out
and they laid it all out on the line. I
mean, just an inspiring effort from our
total team today. Something I wish we
could have did a couple of weeks
earlier, but they came out and they
played really hard against the Chicago
Bears team. The Bears team that's number
one in our division right now, but they
came out and played hard and got that
victory for Dan Campbell and the rest of
this
organization tonight.
>> last year's stiffening NFC North champs,
takes down the current ones. The only
NFC North wins Detroit was able to
muster up this season, but they move to
9 and 8 on the season. That means they
finish with a winning record. Let's talk
about that run game. Finally over 100
rushing yards, which we haven't seen in
a few weeks here at Lomas. Detroit took
good care of the ball. Amon-Ra St. Brown
led the passing attack. Jared Goff was
stellar in that pocket today, too.
>> was. I mean, again, I just love the
tempo of
of our offense. Getting to the line of
scrimmage, giving Jared enough time, so
if he needed to check into a better
play, he can do that. I just love the
aggressiveness aggressiveness that we
had offensively. Some of the slant
routes, the crossing routes. A lot of
the throws that Jared Goff made to those
guys enabled those guys to get yards
after the catch. So, it was just a great
effort, and like you said, with our run
game, Dani, we know we're predicated off
the run, and those guys came out and
established the line of scrimmage. I
thought David Montgomery and Jamaal
Williams did a great job of running hard
when they had the opportunity.
>> Defensively, it started up front for
Detroit. Aidan Hutchinson tacked on
another sack, 14 and a half on the
season. That eclipses his career high,
and the defense held Chicago Bears, who
is led by D'Onta Foreman in that ground
game, to just 65 yards on the day, and
that was a big piece of this defensive
game plan.
>> It really was. I mean, I thought our
front line, and that's what we've been
waiting on, Dani. Been waiting all year
long, and I thought our front line
played a total game, meaning they played
they put pressure on Caleb when they
needed to in the passing but they
stopped the run. That's what we knew
that Chicago wanted to come out and do,
establish the line of scrimmage by
running D'Onta Foreman, Smith, by
running Montgomery, however you say his
last name. It doesn't matter cuz we're
going into the off season, but we did a
great job of controlling those guys,
forcing Caleb to have to put it up in
the air. So, our D-line came out
inspired, and they played that way the
whole game.
>> Someone who else was inspired was Jack
Campbell. Over he only had 10 tackles
today. He was relentless in terms of
getting to the ball. Almost came up with
a big INT today. Was around that
recovery from Derrick Barnes and Tyrell
Williams there that gave Detroit the
ball back on turnover on downs, and Jack
Campbell, once again, leading this core,
and that's why he's a first-time Pro
Bowler this season.
>> Absolutely. I mean, that guy, he's a
complete linebacker, and he kind of
reminds me of a linebacker that played
here, Brian Urlacher. A guy that can
play the run, but a guy that can drop
back and play the pass, too. Jack
Campbell is our leader on the defensive
side of the ball. He proves that game
after game. Like I said, he comes up
with the timely hits. He comes up with
the tackles that he needs to do, but
when you need him to drop back in
coverage and cover a tight end or a
running back, he can do that, too, for
you. So, he's just a complete
linebacker, and he's one of the best
players, I think, in the NFC, period.
>> In the secondary, defensive back Avonte
Maddox, who has had to step into a few
roles this season due to injury, came up
with his first INT as a Detroit Lion. He
was in there in the end zone waiting for
the ball to get to him, and came up with
a big turnover.
>> Great film study, Dani, because that
Watch that play. Caleb Williams, uh
used that play against Green Bay for a
game-winning touchdown play. It was just
great film study from Maddox to beat the
receiver to that spot. Like you said,
come up with the big INT that we needed
to stop that drive that drive of the
Chicago Bears. So, just a great job of
the guys paying attention to the the
attention to the small details, but yet
and still going out and being able to
execute it, too. The leader of the
interior defensive line for Detroit is,
no doubt, DJ Reader. In year 10, he
didn't have the biggest smile on his
face walking off this field tonight
because he knows he has to watch some
football from his couch coming up, but I
spoke with Reader postgame. Here's his
thoughts.
DJ, week 18 coming down to the final
play, go ahead field goal from the
special teams unit here today, but what
kind of response did the defense have in
never letting the Bears and that potent
offense lead today? Man.
Well, like we just played, you know,
played for our brothers beside us today,
and offense came along, defense played
extremely good. Shep had us in some good
calls, man, and the guys got after them
for one more time, man, and ended the
year off right.
No postseason after this, so what kind
of motivation did the team use today to
get this win? I mean, you know, that's
just how it goes sometimes, but we're 1
and 0 in 2026, and we just got to keep
it rolling next year.
Speaking of next year, how can this win
fuel you? How can this season and and
what this team accomplished getting over
.500, what can that do? You know, I
think anytime you end the season with a
winning record, man, you got motivation
for the next year.
This year didn't go how we wanted, but
we ended it with a winning record. Guys
got better. A lot of guys finished the
season healthy, and
you know, it's just it's just a
blessing. It's a blessing to play this
game, so we just got to come back and go
harder next year. CJ.
Well, Detroit kept the streak alive, 2
years of never allowing the Bears to
lead, and they are still in it.
And they swept the Bears, so there you
go, 2 and 0 this season against Chicago.
Head coach Dan Campbell is standing by
at the podium. Let's hear from him.
All right.
Good win by the guys, proud of them. You
know, that's the way to finish. Uh
I really I didn't expect anything
different out of them, just knowing the
guys that we had, and I'll tell you
what. Uh
But nonetheless, I'm still proud of them
because,
you know, it's
it's not always the easiest thing. You
get eliminated, and it's hard for some
guys to, you know, you you're back out
in the elements, and it's with the team
that's already clinched, uh
[Music]
you know, um
but I but our guys fought, man, and from
the beginning,
um even when they came back, you know,
we were up two scores, they came back,
our guys didn't bat an eye, and we were
able to finish it out. It was really one
of the best games we played as far as
complimentary football. That's really
what
um
A lot of a lot of really good
performances
by a lot of guys. Questions? What about
the just the defense in particular, Dan,
especially the run defense? That was a
team that came in, I think, averaged
about 150 yards. 65 yards was the lowest
they've had all year long. You really
seemed to control that by the way, and
they couldn't really get going because
of it, it seemed, especially early.
Yeah, I mean, that was that was big, you
know, it's it's always going to be an
emphasis during the week, but we knew
that was, you know, that's what you have
to do to control that offense. You have
to be able to control the run game, and
for us, we knew we wanted to get going.
Really proud of Decker and Graham. Man,
Hubbard, you know,
getting his first start in a while off
the practice squad, ready to go. Uh you
know, we'll see the tape, but I I
thought he did some really good things,
but the O-line in general, you know,
really showed up for us today. You
mentioned the complimentary football.
Why were you guys able to hold stifle
them offensively for the first two
quarters there?
Defensively? Or
yeah, their offense, yeah. Well, we
Look, we were able to get off the field,
and so,
um you know, we didn't get any of these
these
explosive runs. You know, they hit a
couple, but it, you know, okay, 70-yard
gain, and then we're able to get two
more stops, right? We get off the field,
and so, man, the three and outs were
big, and then we were able to control it
on offense. We had some long drives,
took up a lot of the clock. Conversions,
we got to turn those into touchdowns,
but ultimately, makes it hard. When
you're the other play caller on the
other sideline, and your offense can't
stay on the field, you know, you just
went through three plays, and you're
like, "Okay, what's what's going on?
What's what You know, you start going
through the What should we get to?" We
only ran three plays. So, and then you
come back, and now you only run six
plays. It It's hard to figure out what
you want to get to, what you're trying
to set up for the next time if you're
able to just go three and out or six and
out, you know?
And so, that was big for our defense.
They really set the tone for the day,
and
there again, just complimentary
football. What about offensively, being
able to control the time of possession,
especially here? I think it was 11
plays, 16 plays, nine plays, 11 plays on
your scoring drives. Just being able to
maintain the football much better than
you have been probably the last couple
of years or so. Third down was really
good for us. Really good. You know, our
protection was great and and Goff was
man he was on it, you know. And uh
just his pocket presence, awareness,
getting rid of the ball, knowing where
to go, processing the whole thing. And
then our playmakers making plays, you
know, our our guys making plays. And
that includes Leaf. Leaf's had some big
plays for us, you know, obviously Jamo.
Saint was huge once again. When is he
not huge? Uh
just you know, uh but it yeah I felt
like everybody had a hand in that.
Gibbs,
you know, uh even Fer.
Um so, you know, we were able to spread
it around and uh Goff found them.
So, it was it was good job.
Obviously, 2022 was a different
situation, but going out on a high note
you know, kind of lays a groundwork to a
better season next year. Do you feel
like you know, winning the season opener
connect leading to the next year at all
when you go out on a high note
with a win that last Well, I'll say
this. I believe that things happen for a
reason.
Right, wrong, or indifferent, or what.
And
and I just when something like this
happens, I believe it's it's going to be
for the best. And
it's up to Brad and I to make it for the
best and the guys that we know we're
going to count on that are on this team.
Um
so, that that's how I view it because as
good as it felt to get that and it's the
last one, it's I mean, let's call it
what it is. Pretty pissed all week, you
know, and it's and it's a bad feeling.
And now we're going in the playoffs and
you get to watch everybody else go while
you're sitting at home.
And it's frustrating. So, that's what
fuels you.
We don't want to be doing that again
next year. That's not where we want to
be.
You got to get in.
What stood out to you today in your mind
that maybe hadn't seen for several weeks
with this team?
Um well, probably just that
complimentary football. I mean,
honestly, when we needed it most, all
three phases really showed up for us in
a big way. I mean,
it was like clockwork. Um
you know, we were able to control
uh
you know, control the time of
possession. The the not that we were
necessarily trying to do that, but have
these long drives and and
you know, and about the time
um
you know, something bad happens on
offense, the defense steps right up and
and just comes up with a big takeaway or
you know, a big stop. Um and then when
we get scored on, our offense goes right
down the field when we needed it, you
know, that that series at the end
where we you know, we had the the the
turnover, defense holds them,
you know, forces the punt, and then we
go back, Goff hits Saint for that huge
play. We got some pops and runs there to
get us some field goal range. And then
Bates after the one he had earlier steps
up in a critical and and makes it. I
mean, that's
that's that's what winning teams do, you
know, and and we haven't had that in a
while. It's been a while. It's been a
few weeks.
Did you learn anything about your
Did you learn anything about your team
this week or did it just reaffirm? No, I
think it reaffirmed.
Um you know, I
we'll know some things just watching the
tape about how some of these guys did,
particularly some of the young guys. Um
But the guys that I I knew we could
count on
showed up again.
You know, one more time, which didn't
surprise me one bit. And
um
you know, I still believe the nucleus of
this team is right. I really do.
But but we we're going to need to make a
few changes, you know, and that's not
just talking about that. It'll be
collectively. We going to have to we're
going to have to work through some
things to get the best version of
ourselves.
You got a lot of old friends on that
sideline. Did that give you or the team
any extra juice do you think coming into
this one at all? I mean, I don't, you
know, honestly, I I've been so whatever
with what happened last week and just
trying to get prepared for this one, you
know, and get our guys ready to go. Um I
I don't know. You'd have to ask them.
Um
but listen, I wish them well, you know,
a lot of a lot of people that I think a
lot of over there, you know, between
obviously
you know, Ben and and
and the guys that were with us, JT and
Al, but then man, that
half that staff from New Orleans, they
were you know, I know those guys. I I
coached with them in New Orleans. So, I
I wish them the best of luck and uh
you know, I respect the hell out of
them. They're good coaches.
Good men.
Guys, your prior success has put you at
the top of the power rankings list.
That's a good thing, right? Well, just
means you've gone from the underdog to
the favorite.
But those expectations come from prior
success. So, that's okay.
What about Cure? Where do you guys rank
on the power list? Actually, we just got
named by Forbes as one of the best car
insurance companies in America. Now,
you're the favorite. Guess we have a lot
in common.
Go Cure. Go Lions.
[Music]
Cure Auto Insurance. Drive well.
Detroit Lions Live is brought to you by
Cure Auto Insurance.
Log on to cure.com to see how you can
save.
Detroit's ground attack was challenged
this week. Could it get back to its old
self before the season ended? Well,
challenge accepted by Jahmyr Gibbs and
David Montgomery. Gibbs 80 yards on the
ground, Montgomery tacked on another 42.
Lots of razzle-dazzle, especially with
Montgomery in this game trying to pull
off some flea flickers, you know, direct
snaps to Montgomery. They were trying to
get him another passing TD, but Gibbs
his touchdown in the second quarter, a
15-yard pass from Jared Goff, was the
only touchdown for Detroit on the day.
It was the only one that they needed.
What did you see from Gibbs and the line
of scrimmage that helped this ground
attack just eat some yards tonight?
>> Oh, I mean, again, Danny, they were
sticking their foot in the ground and
getting downhill. And that's what you
need your running backs to do,
especially when you're shuffling your
offensive line the way we've been doing
pretty much this whole season. You you
can't have those long developing plays.
You have to have more quick-hitting
plays. And that's what uh Jahmyr Gibbs
was doing. That's what David Montgomery
was doing, too. So, I think that helped
our run game out tremendously by them
guys, like I say, sticking their foot in
the ground, getting downhill, hitting
the holes that were there. And if they
had opportunity, being able to cut back
because the offensive line gave them
that opportunity. Second quarter
touchdown, our play of the game. It was
right after an Amon-Ra St. Brown
third-down catch from Jared Goff, which
was a dime. Goff went to the air again,
went to the air again, rather, to find
Gibbs for this touchdown pass.
>> Yeah, man, I just love the way Jared
Goff played. And again, he bought time,
Danny. If they said this man couldn't
move around in the pocket, I thought he
did a great job of moving around, buying
time, either moving to the left, moving
to the right, or even moving back when
he had to. He had those twinkle toes
moving tonight, and it did him well
because he bought just enough time to
find guys like Amon-Ra, to find guys
like Jahmyr Gibbs come across on some of
those longer routes. So, kudos to Jared
Goff, kudos to that offensive line. I
thought they played a complete game.
Speaking of Amon-Ra St. Brown, he was
Jared Goff's safety blanket all night
long. 11 catches good for 139
yards. St. Brown looked like his old
self again, coming up with third-down
catch after third-down catch. And he was
a spark plug that this offense needed.
They needed him a little bit sooner than
today, but they they got the OG St.
Brown back.
>> They did. They really did. And he just
continues to stack numbers on top of
numbers. Man, the routes that that guy
runs. That's why he gets open. People
ask, why is he open all the time?
Because he he runs precise routes. And
he runs routes that gets himself open.
He's so smart at reading the defense. If
it's man coverage, he's going to have to
set the defensive back up on him. If
it's zone coverage, he knows how to find
the the soft spots in the zone coverage.
Sit it down for Jared Goff. And they
just seem to have such a chemistry,
especially on some of those out routes,
those timing routes where it's all ultra
important for them to have that
chemistry going on. Those guys seem to
be the best at doing it.
>> St. Brown needed 14 catches to eclipse
his career high in receptions in a
season. He falls just three short, but
over 200 receiving yards between these
two today. Jameson Williams 74 yards on
the day. 23 yards was his longest catch.
What did you see from Jamo in terms of
impacting the the the receiving game?
>> Yeah, Danny, he's getting better and
better all season long. Jamo, he is a
complete receiver now. This guy can run.
Everybody used to just think he was just
a speedster, a guy that you send on a go
route. You know, now this guy has built
himself and built his receiving and
route tree up to to me to where he could
almost run any route that needs to be
run. He's a I'll tell you what, when
next year when you get him and you get
Saint rolling, it's going to be hard for
defenses to decide on who you want to
double team, who you want to try to jam
up, who you want to play man on, who you
want to play zone on. Those are the type
of problems that both of those guys can
present. And I'm just so proud of how
Jamo throughout this whole year has
continued to get better and better each
and every week.
>> 91 yards after catch between Jamo and
Amon-Ra St. Brown, which is music to
this man's man's ears. Jared Goff 42
passing attempts tonight. He was good
for 27 on them. Came up with over 330
passing yards and one touchdown. What
did you see from Goff who opted for two
gloves tonight?
>> two gloves. Hey, I see you with I've
been seeing all year long from Jared
Goff. The consistency, right? That even
demeanor that he has and he carries into
each game. And then like coach Campbell
said, it's almost like having the
offensive coordinator out there on the
field when you have Jared Goff because
Jared makes some of the plays that he
calls in right. He puts them in the
right position that they need to be in
to have success. So, I've seen
everything that I've seen the whole year
long from Jared Goff, which is a
consistent, top-notch quarterback in
this league. Somebody we should be happy
that we have here on on our team.
>> Yeah. Big year 10 for Goff. How did you
just see him progress a little bit here
this season? He's like a a mature
father, you know, a father. Yes, he is.
He you can just see. Now he has a kid.
So, he's like that mature father out
there. Year 10, like you say. And you
just the game slows down for you, Danny.
It's almost like you've seen that, done
that, been there. And that's what I
think is happening to Jared Goff. The
game has slowed down for him. He's able
to dissect defenses and he's able to
attack the defenses with the right
plays. And like I said, you have to be a
quarterback that can put other guys in
position to have success. And that's one
of the best things that he does. Goff
successfully 23 straight games with a
passing TD, but he had to do a lot of
this season with an O-line that was
interchanged. Lots of injuries, trying
to figure out who fits where best,
dating back to training camp. How did he
maneuver that for the season?
>> that's difficult. That's really tough to
do if you think about it cuz one number
one, you have to take care of your job,
right? But not not just his job, right?
He got 10 other guys up there that he
has to help put in position and make
sure those guys in the right position.
So, I thought Jared took on more of a
leadership role, especially from again,
almost kind of like a coaching
standpoint where to where you got a
coach on the field. A guy that's helping
these guys get in the right position.
And think about just like you said, so
many different lineups. We had nine, 10
different lineups from your offense to
mine. He had skill positions that got
hurt. Losing Sam LaPorta and all that.
One of his main blankets that he had.
But yet and still, Jared was able to
adjust, go to the next guy, and help
elevate the next guy as we seen in a guy
like Isaac TeSlaa later on the season
becoming more and more active in this
offense. So, it always does good when
you have a veteran quarterback like a
Jared Goff that like I said, been there,
done that. That guy can help kind of
smooth the ways offensively for you.
>> Yeah. Head coach Dan Campbell, he helped
elevate Ben Johnson to the position he's
in right now. What do you think this win
means to coach Campbell?
>> Oh, it would mean it has to mean a lot.
Come on now, you're
Look, you're to the mentor. You don't
want your mentee to beat you, right? So,
you know, it has to mean a lot for them
to come here, especially because the
season hadn't gone the way we thought
the season was going to go. But yet and
still, the goal of going here against
the division leaders and beat them not
once, but beat them twice. Beat them in
a game where you really didn't have a
lot on the line for us, but they had
everything on the line for them with
their seeding. So, it was just great. I
know and I know coach has to feel good
about that and it has to kind of
springboard you towards next year.
>> Well, Jared Goff's got to feel good
about this win as well. His former
getting one against his former offensive
coordinator. Goff is standing by the
podium. Let's hear from him.
All right.
How good did it feel to get a win in
that environment and just close the
season out on a Yeah, it felt good, man.
It felt good to
finish it that way and
thought we played well in all phases. I
thought we we left some points out there
offensively, certainly in the red zone,
but defense played really well and and
gave us a couple more chances there and
um yeah, we made it happen. Beat you
with the big one. Seven
super efficient today, especially in the
first half. Just what what kind of
helped you guys get off on the right
foot and get it going?
>> Yeah, you know, we were mixing it up
pretty good. I thought the play calling
was really good and um the run game was
working, the play action was working,
the drop back was working.
We our time of possession was really
good. We were holding on to the ball. We
were converting on third down.
Um
all the stuff that's typically indicate
indicative of a good offense, we were
doing that in the first half and just
wish we could have punched in those red
zone ones. Seven different pass
catchers, your guys kind of making plays
when when they needed to. Just how nice
is it to end the year that way
offensively? Giving the football to your
playmakers and having to make plays to
win games. Yeah, I mean sure certainly
there at the end getting to St. Brown to
close it out felt really good and um
yeah, we got a lot of lot of really good
skill players and being able to get them
out out in space was was nice.
Does he ever cease to amaze you how he
can just keep coming into games banged
up? Like I'm thinking back to
>> Who? St.? Yeah. This week too and just
have the kind of performance that he did
today. Yeah, we're kind of used to it
and it's probably taking it for granted
a little bit, but
he doesn't complain. He doesn't He
doesn't say a word about it. He shows up
to practice. It's, you know, 10° out
there. You guys were out there. He's
practicing hard. He's doing everything
right. Like you you you would never know
either way.
Um which just speaks to how special he
is as a human. How good is this? I had a
few old friends on that sideline, Ben,
JT. Do you feel like you guys had any
extra juice coming into this game
because of that?
>> No, I don't think so. Um I really don't.
I think
he's he's a great coach. He's doing
great things.
I have really good uh memories obviously
with him and um they've got uh
they've got the playoffs to look forward
to and we don't, but we were just trying
to get a W. I think it was more so just
in division. You want to win that one,
less about who it is over there, but um
yeah.
What what do you think of the
They played great today, man. They
really did. Yeah, they played really
well. Um
all those guys played well. However, I
thought stepped up in a huge way at
right tackle and
um they were leaning on the run game. It
was really good. They we were opening it
up for those guys. Downhill, you could
see the line of scrimmage moving and
then the pass protection was really good
as well. So, they they had a really good
day today and um I was proud of those
guys.
Any advice for David on the sack that he
took there? Yeah, throw it away.
Uh yeah, no. I I It's always hard for
those skill guys to
uh be able to think like they're
throwing it and then they got to throw
it away, but yeah, you know, you wish
you threw it away, but whatever.
I wish he would give me a jump ball
opportunity just down the field.
How good are you guys? All good. Thank
you guys.
Guys, your prior success has put you at
the top of the power rankings list.
That's a good thing, right? Well, just
means you've gone from the underdog to
the favorite. But those expectations
come from prior success. So, that's
okay. What about Cure? Where do you guys
rank on the power list? Actually, we
just got named by Forbes as one of the
best car insurance companies in America.
Now you're the favorite. Guess we have a
lot in common.
Go Cure. Go Lions.
[Music]
Cure Auto Insurance. Drive well.
Detroit Lions Live is brought to you by
Cure Auto Insurance.
Log on to cure.com to see how you can
save.
Did
Detroit ends their season on a high
note, finishing with a winning record, 9
and 8, sweeping the Bears. They couldn't
repeat that NFC North title division,
and there's going to be some really
tough questions that this staff and
these players are going to have to ask
themselves and each other when this
thing's all over, Lomas.
>> No, it is, Danny. You're right about
that. The one thing that you don't want
to go into the off season on a loss. So,
Detroit avoided that. Two, you wanted to
go up against the best in your division.
We did that going up and beating Chicago
Bears both times. So, again, you're
right. There's going to be a lot of
tough decisions. There might be some
people that might not be here next year.
But again, you know how to move forward.
This team, when they come out and they
play and they execute to the best of
their ability, we're one of the best
teams in the NFL and we know that now
going up against this Chicago Bear team.
A lot of things didn't go right for us.
You could talk about injuries. You could
talk about losing the coordinators. So,
there's a lot of things you can talk
about, but this team has grit. This team
has heart and they have the nucleus here
that you could build around and I expect
the coaching staff, Brad Holmes, and the
rest of the brass to go out and make
sure that they get that taken care of
for the 2026 season.
>> When you do look at this off season,
what is the number one area that this
team needs to attack in order to
improve? Danny, the lines of scrimmage.
And when I say that, the offensive line
and the defensive line. Getting Aidan
Hutchinson a little help up there
up on the defensive line with him.
Getting the middle of our offensive line
back together. We know we got our
stalwart Penei Sewell, but we'll tailor
there could be that we we have to get a
left tackle. Getting those guys in the
middle of that offensive line to shore
things up there so we could give Jared
Goff the protection he needs and also
open the holes up for Jahmyr Gibbs and
the David Montgomery.
>> Ooh, it's going to be an interesting off
season to see what moves Detroit decides
to make. Thank you so much for watching
all season long our Detroit Lions Live
postgame show presented by Cure Auto
Insurance for the last one. That's Lomas
Brown, the Super Bowl champ. I'm Dannie
Rogers.
Great win to go out on this season.
Detroit gets it done at Chicago. 19 to
16 is the final. Happy off season,
Detroit, or not very happy off season.
But enjoy it. A lot of work to do before
Dan Campbell and his Lions take the
field again for next season. Good night,
everyone.
[Music]
>> I want
I want